hovory Yasuie Fire
One Piece!
All of
Oh!
Oh, as-as!
As-as, as-as-as!
Noooo...
Watch where you're stepping!
You could've killed us!
Oops!
Sorry!
Look at you.
Bonnie's not the only one
who's hit a growth spurt.
ULA a finger on old mad apple.
Listen, kids, some of us have jobs.
Let me go back to doing mine, please.
Let you go.
Oh, OK!
Ah!
We're ready!
It's not necessary!
Whoa, take it easy!
Look at him flying!
We have to run now! Let's
hurry! Yeah, you're right!
Let's go while Luffy keeps Kizaru busy.
Okay, but we have to be gentle with Robin.
Hey, Atlas! You see me?
I'm going down below.
I have to take control of the pacifistas.
Otherwise, as soon as
the barrier goes down...
Your lasers will blow us to smithereens!
That's good thinking!
Us Vegapunks are the highest
authority on the island after all.
And whoever controls
the pacifist, it will!
Hell yeah!
We've got this!
Atlas space!
That is what I mean to say.
Please, take me with you! What?
You cannot go! Why not?
Are you kidding me?
There are 30,000 Marines out
there who all want you dead!
I know, but...
Come in, Franky!
This is Vegapunk, can you hear me?
What's up?
I just saw Bonnie down in the city!
She's alive then?
What a relief, she hit the
barrier, Kizaru kicked her hard!
Kizaru did hurt to her and
you just took the handbunch!
You are a blue man!
I'm sorry, okay?
I'll go save her right now! You'd better!
But what are we gonna
do about the barrier?
I've made up my mind, I'm going! What?
They'll have Edison
deactivate the barrier!
Hey, it's Surge!
I heard what you said.
All of it.
You're going to go in
and rescue her, right?
Then you can count me in.
Our work here is done.
We picked up the luggage you
asked us to and we're on our way.
I'll head toward the
rear exit immediately.
Let's all meet up there.
Go! Go! Go!
Did something just move? Hey!
What are you doing?
It's this way. Hurry up! Yes, sir.
I guess it's dangerous here, too.
Come get some!
What was that scream?
Come in.
What's going on?
Stop!
I know you.
Sure.
Central units, give me
a report. What happened?
Well done.
Ah!
Dammit!
Reporting in!
We've all been turned into
children or old people!
What?
Everyone invade the center of town.
It's a trap!
All central units were
ambushed by Jewelry Bonnie!
Search the surrounding zones cautiously.
She has the power to change your age!
She can't have got to war!
Find Jewelry Bonnie and take her down!
Damn it. Hey!
Over here!
A fan said to Moria!
But he...
It looks like he's been burned.
Sentomaru.
Sentomaru?
Run away, Bonnie.
The Marines are coming.
What should I do? Have you found her?
Not yet, sir. Check that way. Yes, sir.
I wonder if I can hide
until this is all over.
Hey, just fight me already.
You have nothing to
gain from this, Roronoa.
Stay out of our way and let us do our job.
It doesn't matter if you hide.
Doesn't matter how fast you run.
I know right where you are.
Cause you stink like a beast!
Huh?
Whoa, was that Pigeon Guy?
Zoro, do you want my help?
Good luck, cat sitting.
Ah!
It's focus on Kizaru.
He's the real problem!
Ha!
You're barely keeping up.
If this is the best you can do, you're
never gonna get another shot at our captain.
Ha ha ha.
But I've still got you.
An Emperor's first mate.
That's a worthy trophy.
I might drown.
That won't do at all.
Yasakani, Sacred Jewel.
Hey, that's bright!
I don't know how to do it.
No! My face!
I've seen these!
Hot glands!
Stupid shining heart away!
Oh, come on, again with this?
Well, it's fine.
The bigger target is easier to hit.
So, thank you for that.
Huh?
I don't know which one's real!
Just kidding!
I'll hit them all!
Dum-zum! Done!
Yeah!
I thought I was the one tricking you!
Now this is unfortunate.
I leave for one second
and Vegapunk is gone.
Could you tell me where he is, please?
I need a little help right now!
Oh, Bad Apple!
Wait!
Hey, Vegapunk!
Let me in there!
You're really worked up!
Not that I blame you, though.
Won't you touch her, you
port-linking Navy scum?
Never fear, Bonnie!
I'm on my way! Stay strong!
I should have protected you!
You poor darling child!
Poor darling child!
Get in already!
I'll let you in the bubble!
Just shove yourself through!
Well, if you say so.
What are you doing?!
Stay in the dope thing!
You're gonna get killed out here!
Did you think I'd just let you run?
This is over, old man.
Do something still, I can't go with that!
That's already...
Doha!
Change of plans!
We'll use General Franky
to carry the Sonny!
Time!
Catch and interact with these bros! Okay!
Ah!
Angus-san, do it! Right away!
Frontier Dome!
Partially deactivate!
Activate!
Can this thing fly?
Wait, what's that?
Something's up there.
Hold on, I think I can see inside.
It's Dr. Vegapunk!
I have a report from the Fabriophase!
It's urgent!
We've just spotted Vegapunk!
He's descending from the
Labophase in a vehicle!
Take aim!
Prepare to fire!
You have a new order,
direct from Dr. Vegapunk.
Every Marine on the
island must be eliminated!
Oh, this is bad.
I think it's on your nose.
New target designated.
Eliminate all Marines on Egghead.
Get away from the pacifistas!
They have a new order. Dr.
Vegapunk must have taken control back.
So many pacifistas!
How are we supposed to fight them all?
Damn you, Vegapunk!
Yeah!
Now it's a party!
Let her rip past the vistas!
Seems they're all
responding to the command.
Yeah!
Hold up!
It looks like we're going straight down.
We're not gonna dive bomb
into the ground, are we?
We are on island clouds.
It's in their nature to
attach to one another.
Since our tiles are also made of clouds,
we won't fall to our deaths
even if we head straight down.
But enough about our ride!
We must find Bonnie!
She's surely alone and
terrified down there!
Hey, Bonnie!
Where are you? Bonnie!
Bonnie!
I need to focus.
Don't think. Feel.
I'll reach out across the entire universe
and sense her with the waves of my soul.
My lady dark on a ping I found her!
Same for me you sure don't question me
my lady door has never been wrong once.
I dispute the science of your methods,
but I will trust your instinct.
Thanks, Doctor.
Now, if you'll all excuse me, this tank
just can't keep up with my impatient heart.
Don't worry, Meat!
I'm on my way!
What a relief.
Looks like the pacifistas
are back on our side.
Thought you could hide huh?
This is over, jewelry.
Bonnie, you'll pay for what
you did to our men over there!
Hey, what the hell's wrong with you three?
I think I just went to hell.
Get back here!
I'm not done with you!
You cannot escape!
Huh? Why?
Ha!
I can't command all the pacifistas, but
I snuck around the rules for this one.
I have the power to
control anything I sit on,
because I'm a driving human
who ate the radron fruit.
Now, here's a little question.
Will the curse you pleased on
our men be lifted if I kill you?
Dad.
Last chance, kiddo!
Keep them back now!
Huh?
Come on, Bonnie.
Don't zone out on us now.
Black leg.
Look, I get it.
It's because Kuma's your father, right?
You have to remember they're not him.
If you can't...
Armor-clamber!
Marines everywhere.
Time for us to go.
Go, pacifista!
Fire!
Ah, man!
Kicking the bubble, let's roll! Hurry!
The pacifist will fire on us!
Let's head back up!
Oh, just shake it off already!
Whoa! Oh!
Oh, my God.
It's no use resistance,
your fate is already sealed.
This guy never learns.
Uh-oh.
Huh?
Look, I don't know why you're doing
this, but I've got orders to follow.
I don't care!
The clock is ticking.
Struggle while you can.
You sure like to talk, don't you?
If you'll excuse me,
I have a mission to wrap up I bet
you were wasting too much of my time!
That's the idea!
It's my mission to get in your way!
Oh
What to do
What's wrong?
It's weird!
Something doesn't feel right.
What is this?
Such an unnatural presence.
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
All units, stand down.
The pacifistas aren't
protecting us anymore.
They're not even moving.
Come on, I gave you an order!
Eliminate all the marines.
You're supposed to keep us safe.
Something's happening?
There's only one group above
Vegapunk on the authority ladder.
And that's.
The Five Elders!
What is that?
It's a pentagram!
What the hell?
Step on it!
Get to high ground! I'll try!
Attention, all Marines!
Saint Saturn is on his way!
He will arrive on Egghead shortly!
Not a single Marine below the rank
of Commodore may be in his presence!
He's coming here? I repeat!
Saint Saturn of the Five Elders
will make landfall on Egghead!
What was that explosion?
One of the five elders, so I'm
shocked that they came and passed.
The five elders?
Never heard of them.
Who are they?
The highest authorities in the bird.
Wait, for real?
Something big's coming out!
what the hell is that it's some
kind of monster Cut it out!
That must be...
Ah, the surface.
It's been quite a while.
That's huge.
What is that thing?
Above us! Dodge!
Oops.
That was a close one.
We don't have any clouds to get us!
He's over!
I found you!
Get back here!
Boy, you gotta be running out of juice.
That form won't hold up.
Do something, Luffy!
What am I gonna do?
I got you!
Huh?
Nope, I don't like that.
Nika.
Oh, my poop.
You okay, Doc? Still breathing?
So it would seem...
Atlas, are you hurt? I'm okay.
Are you St. Saturn?
I am.
I thought you were already dead, Vegapunk.
What a shame.
I gave you an order, Vegapunk
Bonnie, wait!
You must eliminate Kuma's free will
But if I do that to him, thank you.
I'll kill you!